Wait, hold on. I don't get it.
Why are you helping us?
Didn't La Morte Bianca send you
to kill me and Chiara?
Oh wait.
Aren't you with someone?
Is this solo travel?
Oh no, Auntie.
I'm with someone.
Actually, he's on his way here.
He said he'll text me once he arrived.
What if Agent Alex can get Mikoy back?
That's not going to happen.
Why?
Because that fool is so in love,
And when we think about it,
the world will be a better place
without all of you.
What are you waiting for?
What's this?
A bribe?
What I want is a suitcase.
Hey, that's ilegal.
And I'm just a lowly employee.
What are you thinking?
What I mean by suitcase is,
like, pack my luggage,
so I can follow to Hong Kong right away.
Oh dear.
Even if I pack five suitcases for you,
it wouldn't do any good
because what you need
is a round-trip plane ticket,
which I cannot afford.
Okay, fine.
If you don't believe us either,
then just shoot us.
Or just call the police,
instead of us standing here
when nothing was happening anyway.
Yes, I'll be back.
Sorry because…
I was so snappy earlier.
You were being so persistent.
Not even a minute had passed and then,
you started asking me about Agent Alex.
Was that right?
I thought you were apologizing to me?
Why does it sound like
you're annoyed and angry now?
There you go.
I'm just explaining.
But I really came here to apologize.
Because I realized that I should've been
more patient and understanding
of your situation.
Because I've experienced before
what you're going through now.
Having feelings for Alex?
No!
What I mean to say is,
we're both in love
with someone who didn't reciprocate.
Me?
That's not me, okay?
That's not me.
You know, I was thinking,
while Donatello is still peeing,
why don't we settle this standoff of ours?
You know, so we can be efficient.
Oh, Agent Alex.
Donatello?
Quickly!
Okay.
- Coming.
- Straight ahead.
I have a sharp memory,
and it hasn't been a while
since you made that heartfelt confession
to Agent Alex.
I don't even know what I liked about her.
Love is really complicated.
It can completely break your standards.
Even when you least expect it.
Your heart just suddenly starts beating.
You suddenly fall for someone
you never expected.
And one day you'll realize
you've developed feelings for them.
Walk.
Faster!
Stay right there.
I think I get why you're
attracted to Agent Alex.
- Why?
- Because you're both falling for someone
who can't return your affection.
But I admire your courage.
Not everyone can confess,
not everyone can take that first step,
and what people ultimately look for
in a relationship is something lasting,
like… friendship.
And you,
you've already told Agent Alex
how important she is to you.
So now you already exist in her orbit,
as more than just a friend.
I don't have a gun.
Wait, time out!
- Mikoy!
Sweetheart, why did you
put your face in the way?
We need to leave.
You can't leave.
Alex, I'm not lying to you.
I'm telling the truth that Chiara
is no longer a Moraviano.
Alex, come on.
Let's talk this through first.
Clear! Move, move, move, move!
Wait, wait.
Who were you talking to
through your earpiece?
You have backup?
That's why I brought guns,
not just one, but two.
As a matter of fact,
they gave me their full support.
There's a tactical squad positioned
right outside this room.
So you have nowhere to run.
I admire your courage.
You told Agent Alex
how important she is to you.
So now you exist in her orbit,
as more than just friends.
There's an update from Agent Alex.
‪Hold on.
Here it is.
Donatello escaped.
You are my targets.
Arresting Il Pittore
would just be a bonus.
Now tell me.
Because we can help you.
Chiara and I can help you
bring down the real villains
of this story.
It's La Morte Bianca and the Concordat.
I wouldn't be asking if I had.
- Actually.
- True.
Or maybe an influencer?
What did she say?
I didn't understand either.
You know what? I'll just go
catch up with our tricycle.
Let's go!
Sorry, madam.
- Here are the snacks.
- Are you sure you don't need help?
You sit down. You're our guests.
I'll take care of it.
- Okay.
- Our rice cakes.
Put those down, Betchay.
Wow, so this is what it's like
in the province?
You have snacks together
and everyone joins in.
Of course.
Like they always say, right?
I see.
I thought people only ate
when they felt dizzy or had a headache.
Oh my, Berto, did you hear
what your daughter just said?
Are you taking care of her properly?
Oh. No, no, it's not Dad Sir.
I'm the one with the problem.
Even Sofie needs to eat
at the proper time.
Roger that.
What a small world, huh?
Imagine, you turned out to be the parents
of Sofie's FUBU.
What's a FUBU?
It means fun buddy, Mom.
Fun buddy is what it means.
Okay.
Didn't you tell me before?
I can't remember anymore.
Anyway, it means something like,
you started out as friends.
Like Mario and me back then.
We were FUBUs too.
Daddy Sir, that's an old term,
and it's not cool these days.
All right.
You said it.
Well, all I wanted to say is that
Mario and I…
You and Dad were best friends?
We were best friends.
Back then.
But then, we got busy with our own lives.
We lost communication, so…
There you go again with your excuses.
Well, we applied to the military together.
But Mario here
decided to walk away from it
because he felt
that it wasn't the life for him.
I left because I wanted to start a family.
So if you've known each other that long,
So, was she his first great love?
Here's your order. Thank you and enjoy!
Tess.
Look at Berto Butete.
He's been staring at you for a while now.
Looks like he really likes you.
Looks like you're the one who likes him.
I don't like him.
The one I really like
is the guy coming in yellow!
You're being too harsh on Berto!
- Bro!
- Oh, you!
- You look expensive, bro!
You really are something!
I know your type.
The rough-and-tough kind!
Listen to that mouth of yours!
Why?
The kind who roughs up bad people.
Oh, stop it!
Fine, Catacutan is all yours.
So, Berto is for me!
Because I really feel like
he's the meringue on top of my--
That better not be something naughty!
My bread roll!
Okay.
He winked at me!
Mom, you're spacing out.
Are you having flashbacks?
No, dear. You know,
I was just reminiscing.
I remembered Maya.
You know, dear,
Maya was one of the kindest people
I've ever met in this world.
I wish I had met her too.
My Mom died while giving birth to me.
But for now, of course, I want
to hear stories about her.
Mikoy, is what she said
about the Concordat true?
That there's an even bigger group
than the Moravianos?
Mikoy, answer me.
Hold on.
Why are you looking at Mikoy?
Why are you only asking him?
Do you think I'm a liar and he's not?
And after all the lies you've told
to protect your family
and the Moravianos,
how can I trust you?
Wait, wait.
But to be fair, Agent Alex, same with me.
I can lie as well.
Go ahead.
Alex.
I'm not mad at you
because I already know
that you have feelings for me.
You just don't know how I feel
when I'm with you.
Darn it! Let me try again.
Please, Mikoy, don't you dare.
Besides, that's not helping
your situation with Chiara.
Who is La Morte Bianca?
Yes! Of course she is.
Isn't she just a fictional mafia character
created to give the illusion
of fear and discipline?
Nope. She's absolutely real.
Well, I've never met her face-to-face.
I haven't even met her online.
But after Chiara and I came clean
about all our secrets,
she told me everything,
and I mean everything.
Her entire backstory,
including La Morte Bianca.
She even told me about
her erogenous zones.
That's SPG.
Right, right.
But she's really real.
If we thought before that the Moravianos
were our only enemies,
we were very wrong.
There's something worse.
There's a bigger force that is about
to descend upon the entire Philippines.
You want protection for yourself,
for Mikoy, and for your family, right?
Oh no! My gosh!
This brownout is ridiculous.
No warning at all.
But that's how it is, darling.
You see, during summer,
it gets hot, so everyone ends up
using their air conditioners at once.
The power grid can't handle it.
And then,
we end up with a rotating brownout.
Why don't you first prove to me
that the information you're offering
is valuable?
Then I'll decide
whether it's truly worthy
of immunity from prosecution.
You need vital information, right?
I can give that.
But this is a game changer.
Make sure you're ready.
Why are you here?
Is it an urgent matter?
G.A.G.O. has called an emergency meeting.
About what?
For the case of the Moraviano.
With all this long presentation,
and you just asked me
to protect this couple,
Chiara and Mikoy?